Within the Clover's fifth leaf, there lives a devil.
Asta, born unable to harness mana, was granted the power of anti-magic from his five-leaf grimoire,
giving him the ability to nullify spells.
Unfortunately, the members of Spade Kingdom's Dark Triad also possessed powers from the devils of the Underworld,
and used them to launch an invasion on the neighboring countries.
Gaining strength from his belief in himself and from the support of his friends,
Asta continues to fight for the safety of this world.
We're going to take you down!
The fate of existence itself is in our hands.
Valkyrie armor! Mermaid form!
Noelle and Laura Petchka faced off against Vanica, using the strategy they had prepared.
However…
Are you ready for the big one?
Here we go!
You get my best!
Lucky you!
Here's 78% power!
Do it, Noelle!
We were waiting for this.
Zero!
I'm about to seal away that devil's power you seem so proud of!
Mana method!
Sealing magic!
Eternal prison!
I won't let Queen Laura Petchka or this world be harmed by scum like you!
It worked!
I did it.
I sealed away her magic and the devil's power.
Now, the Heart Kingdom should be safe from Megicula's wrath once and for all.
And the Queen's curse should be gone.
What?
You're obviously weaker than us, and yet you produced some surprising magic.
You put up an interesting fight. I'll give you that much.
This ominous mana! Oh no! Laura Petchka!
Laura Petchka!
Tch!
We're gonna wake it in for the brand new world!
Yeah!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world!
To the brand new world!
We're gonna wake in for the brand new world!
Get your hands up, baby!
We're gonna take you to the brand new world!
Oh, yeah!
Get it on, get it on,始めよう
難航不落のリアリティ
立ち止まる時間はないさ
Hold on, hold on
Yeah!
Now this time, fight for liberty
真実性 飲み込む常識
Overwave
逆境の先にある朝
Oh yeah!
健闘に埋もれた人生の夢
Hands up!
Shout it! Shout it! Louder!
Yes! Do it! Do it! Start it!
Never give up!
限界を超えても
勝つ口的 experience
We can't say
Let's go!
Believe in myself
衝動的に突き進め
Don't be afraid
誰よりも高く飛べ
Take it to the sky
想像を超えた世界をこの手に
The ground up
想像せよいつは意図ない自分の道
Yes! It's a ground up
Hey yeah!
Believe in myself
Feeding yourself
Hey yeah!
Yeah!
What in the world is happening?
You shouldn't have looked away!
Oh no!
I know what will stop you!
You must have thought so carefully about how to defeat us.
You came terribly close to containing my power.
Truly splendid, all of you!
Let's play some more. I haven't had enough yet.
How did we fail? What went wrong?
Nero's magic should have been enough to seal you away.
Curse warding magic, decaying world. It weakens any spell arrays that are used against me.
And it was already active at 70% capacity.
Apparently, it can even weaken the sealing magic of an arcane stage opponent. I'm happy I tried that out.
Slow down, Megicula. You're totally getting in the way. I'm trying to have fun, you know.
Laura...
Pechka...
This is the first time I've ever cursed a water spirit. I see. So that's what happens. I'm learning so much from this experiment.
What?
No. I'm deep.
Where are you?
There.
You are just the cutest.
It's time to study.
Let's take today off.
What? Can we?
Sure we can.
A little break never hurt anybody. All we have to do is come back extra strong tomorrow.
She was always by my side.
You're doing so well, Laura Pechka.
Really? I'm not so sure. Am I good enough?
Of course you are. Believe in your abilities.
She always consoled me when things were tough.
It's beautiful.
Yes. This is our precious kingdom.
Tell me, Undine. Do you think I can protect this place?
I know you can, Laura Pechka.
She was always close to me. Closer than anyone.
Undine.
Oops. Pardon me.
Your curse must have activated because I moved closer to you.
You're in too much pain to move.
And now your water spirit can't help you.
It's all over.
You better not throw in the towel, Laura Pechka. It was just getting good. Come on, you've got a little fight left in you, right?
Hang on, Undine. Don't die.
Don't die.
I guess that's it for her.
Well then, you might as well die too.
Laura Pechka.
Hey, you two.
What?
It's not over yet.
Because you both still have to contend with me.
Please, no one cares about you anymore.
Without Laura Pechka's magic, you're not even a threat now.
See?
Way too slow.
Let me help you!
What a naughty girl trying to interfere that fact.
Trust me, honey. You're about to get a serious tongue lashing for what you've done.
You can't even compete.
So boring.
Not yet.
Say what you want.
I'm not done!
This girl...
You hurt so many people!
And will never forgive you!
Ever!
Aw, cute!
You really gave it your all for that last little push, but it doesn't affect me at all.
I'll protect her.
No matter what!
Point, blame, sea dragons!
Roar!
To defeat!
YZ, what did I tell you?
Those measly attacks won't do any good...
What?
Wait a sec.
Hey, brat. What did you say your name was?
Noelle Silva.
I am a royal of the Clover Kingdom.
And a magic knight. A black bull.
The dragon has written in chron wonders.
. .
Oh, they s according to the enemies of Sacy's Lambda.
Also, chest.
so you managed to injure me again that certainly was an impressive feat however
this magic i'm using it's a bit unsightly i'm going to show you something since it's just you and me
yamizuki hero you're about to witness the awesome power bestowed upon the devil possessed
sounds good i've got something to show you too i call this the power of an ordinary human
we were keeping watch until the right moment to attack spade how did things turn out like this
should i focus on supporting yami or should i try and round up some other squad captains
no i can't if i make a move they'll kill me on the spot
my devil power just increased to eighty percent eighty percent was that supposed to impress me
damn it where's all that mana coming from by the way your eyeliner's running creep
when possessed by a devil once power is shared with a resident of the underworld
by its very nature that exchange must take place between two realms and until the door
is opened we cannot reach one hundred percent though i'm not sure whether that applies to
the little imp over there
now for gravity magic gravity singularity technique you'd be no use as a dead man but i can rip off
a leg at least
seriously i would have taken a lot more than my leg
dark cloak
dimension
wasn't expecting him to warp that
his gravity's way stronger than what he was using at the beginning
if i use black moon they might cancel each other out
but as long as he's generating gravity i can't afford to waste that move
i'll just keep my monosome condensed my senses sharp until i can get behind it
no wait there's no point in cutting him down if he's just going to regenerate
i need something powerful and precise
i'll focus on one spot
focus on one spot
you were surprisingly entertaining to fight yami sukihiro i mean you're just a human but still
yami sukihiro i mean you're just a human but still
yami
now then who's up next
right here and now
i'll push past my limits
if i let my squad down
well then i'd be a piss poor captain wouldn't i
i'll take that condensed monosome and condense it more
focusing it on one spot
i admit that's quite a clever strategy but you'll need a lot more than that my friend
dark magic
death thrust
death
well i said thrust
but it was more like a cannon
whoa
captain yami really is incredible
sorry pal
i couldn't help but you had target written all over you
impossible
there's no human capable of beating me at my best
no
obviously i'm wrong
there is someone and he just blew a hole right through me
that was irritating to say the least
but thank you yami sukihiro
how did that not kill him
my innate ability is body magic and the devil's power makes me even better at restoring myself after a hard hit like that
it's impossible for me to die grow old or deteriorate
but let me be clear
i detest how ugly it is when i morph
the sight of it reminds me that i'm being pushed
so i prefer never to use this magic if i can help it
this is getting way out of hand
i mean come on are you even human at this point
hideous
hideous though it may be
it's quite gratifying
death thrust
you've amazed me once again
you should be proud
your instincts and combat finesse are superior to my own
it's making me jealous
but you see i can't die
otherwise you might have stood a chance
you may be skilled but that means nothing in this fight
the world is just so terribly unfair
try as you might there are still things you can't control
it's the same for me
every once in a while be it because of raw talent or careful training
some foe manages to miraculously point their blade at my throat
in the end i have no choice but to decimate them completely
that my friend is the height of ecstasy
be careful
be careful captain
i can't get close enough to land a hit
but if i move too far away starts chucking rocks at me
damn you
captain yami is still fighting
he pushed past his limits and here i am
stand up
come on stupid body
move
please
you
leave me
see
look
who
was
are dak
Captain Yami...
No!
I'll admit it. I can't win this fight on my own.
This guy's creepy and insane. Plus he can't die and he never runs out of mana.
Hey!
I'm gonna need backup over here.
Oscar?
You got a Deathwish boy.
Hey kid, were you watching?
Look alive kid!
Why are you just standing there like some kind of chicken?
I wouldn't give you more than you could handle.
Do something. Fight him your way kid.
You fell down!
You're not worried about me are you kid?
Cause I'll tell you right now it's about a billion years too early for that.
Ready?
You're both going to challenge me at once? How absolutely delightful!
Entertain me! I'm starting to get bored!
You'd better keep up, pasta.
We've got this captain Yami.
Reefing out your kills
And you come down your kills
And I'm not even toys
We've got this unconditional feels
by consuming and serving
by consuming time
Who you are
夜明け前の空
静かにそっと
ほら新たな日々が始まる
胸にしまい込んだままの
想いを解き放って
その翼を広げて
One more time
今飛び立て
あの海原を見下ろして
誰よりも遠く
何度でも
Will you fly
Beautiful
どんな景色も
君といれば輝くよ
だからずっとそばにいて
and never let go
僕のこの手を
離さないでどこまでも
ついてきてほしい
The world is so beautiful
I want to lick
Come on
and you're looking
awfully lickable
that doesn't work for me
here
maybe you'd like this
this is so yummy
and sweet
a perfect candidate
for a lick
if you ask me
then I bet
this will be even better
it's a sweet too
but the rich flavor
and cold texture
put it very high
on the lickability scale
now that you've got
you've got what you want
we can put an end
to all this pointless
fighting right
actually there's still
one more thing
that's missing
leave this part to me
mimosa
is this what you had in mind
you stupid sicko
it's perfect
unless of course
you will need to
step on me even harder
hehehehehe
hehehe
I figured that was it
thank you noel
looks like you're a lot
fraver than I am
radiasta
it's time for the
counterattack
i'm on it captain yummy
i'm gonna push past my limits
and destroy this freak
once and for all
black clover
page 167
black oath
digitized by
the end
i'm gonna push past hat
is that Coach
is that don't
acid
th
so
that
g